lifamilies.com 2018-12-22

# LIFamilies.com Privacy Policy

INTERNET PRIVACY POLICY

Bridal Planner Group, Inc has developed this privacy statement for you, the visitor, to demonstrate our commitment to privacy on the Internet. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Bridal Planner Group and all other Web sites owned and operated by Bridal Planner Group.

Bridal Planner Group can be contacted by mail at:

Attention Legal Department  
Bridal Planner Group, Inc.  
16 Sawgrass Drive  
Suite 2  
Bellport, NY 11713  
United States of America

by phone at (631) 320-3450 or

by e-mail _here_.

1\. Collection of Personal Information from Site Visitors

Bridal Planner Group may collect and/or track (1) the home server domain names, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, and type of Web browser of visitors to Bridal Planner Group' website, (2) the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with Bridal Planner Group via e-mail, (3) information knowingly provided by the visitor in online forms, registration forms, surveys, and contest entries (including demographic and personal profile data), and (4) aggregate and user-specific information on which pages visitors access.

Bridal Planner Group may place Internet "cookies" on visitors’ hard drives. Internet cookies save data about individual visitors, such as the visitor’s name, password, user-name, shopping cart, screen preferences, the pages of a site viewed by the visitor, and the advertisements viewed or clicked by the visitor. When the visitor revisits Bridal Planner Group's website, Bridal Planner Group may recognize the visitor by the Internet cookie and customize the visitor’s experience accordingly. Visitors may decline Internet cookies, if any, by using the appropriate feature of their Web client software, if available.

When a visitor performs a search within Bridal Planner Group's website, Bridal Planner Group may record information identifying the visitor or linking the visitor to the search performed. Bridal Planner Group may also record limited information for every search request and uses that information only to solve technical problems with the service and to calculate overall usage statistics.

2\. Use of Personal Data Collected

Personal data collected by Bridal Planner Group may be used by Bridal Planner Group for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users’ behavior, for product development, for content improvement, to inform advertisers as to how many visitors have seen or clicked on their advertisements, or to customize the content and layout of Bridal Planner Group's website. Aggregate data on visitors’ home servers may be used for internal purposes or provided to third parties such as advertisers. Individually identifying information, such as names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone numbers, and other personal information which visitors voluntarily provide to Bridal Planner Group may be (i) added to Bridal Planner Group's databases and used for future calls and mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and status of orders placed online, or (ii) provided to reputable third parties who provide products and services which Bridal Planner Group believes that visitors may be interested in purchasing or obtaining, with prior notice to the visitor. 

3\. Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties

Any third party to which Bridal Planner Group shares, rents, sells, or otherwise discloses personal data will be under a contractual obligation to use the personal data for marketing products and services which Bridal Planner Group determines, in its sole judgment, that visitors might find of interest. Bridal Planner Group will use its reasonable efforts to identify such third parties who may have products or services of interest to visitors to Bridal Planner Group's website. However, such parties are independent third parties over which Bridal Planner Group exercises no control, and therefore Bridal Planner Group is not responsible for their conduct, products, or services, and will not be liable therefor. Bridal Planner Group will disclose to third parties only information in aggregate form, that is publicly available, and/or that is knowingly and voluntarily disclosed by visitors. If there are advertisements on Bridal Planner Group's Web site, through the use of third party cookies, the advertiser(s) will be electronically notified when visitors view or click on its advertisements.

4\. Security Measures

Bridal Planner Group has implemented numerous security features to prevent the unauthorized release of or access to personal information. In particular, when a visitor places an order on this site (if any) or accesses his or her account information (if any), Bridal Planner Group offers the visitor the ability to use a secure server. The secure server encrypts all information a visitor inputs before it is sent to Bridal Planner Group, and is also used to securely store personal information. Please be advised, however, that while Bridal Planner Group has endeavored to create a secure and reliable site for visitors, the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to/from Bridal Planner Group via this site or e-mail cannot be guaranteed. Accordingly, Bridal Planner Group is not responsible for the security of information transmitted via the Internet. [For more private communication, visitors can contact us by telephone at (631)331-5703.]

5\. Opt-Out Right

Visitors may opt out of having their personal information collected by Bridal Planner Group, used by Bridal Planner Group for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by Bridal Planner Group or third parties to send promotional correspondences to the visitor, by contacting Bridal Planner Group via postal mail, e-mail, or telephone at the addresses above, or by checking the appropriate box. 

6\. Access to and Ability to Correct Personal Data

Upon request via postal mail, e-mail, or phone, Bridal Planner Group will provide to visitors a summary of any personal information retained by Bridal Planner Group regarding the visitor. Visitors may modify, correct, change or update their personal record or cause their personal record to be removed from Bridal Planner Group's database. Bridal Planner Group will only send personal records to the e-mail address on file for the visitor name associated with it.

7\. Collection of Personal Data from Children

To the extent Bridal Planner Group is able to determine the age of users by their submissions to or communications with Bridal Planner Group's website, Bridal Planner Group will not knowingly (i) collect or post information from individuals under the age of sixteen ("children") without their parent’s or guardian’s consent, or (ii) provide any personally identifying information collected from children, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatsoever. If registration is required for any services on the Bridal Planner Group website, and a user submits information to Bridal Planner Group's website as part of the registration process which indicates that such user is a child, the child’s parent or guardian will receive an e-mail alerting them to the child’s registration and providing instructions on how the parent can delete the child’s registration, if so desired. No information collected through Bridal Planner Group's website from users self- identified as children will knowingly be used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside Bridal Planner Group. If there are no age restrictions on a contest which requires registration, and if a child wins, notification and prizes will be sent to the parent(s) or guardian(s) identified in the initial registration process.

8\. Bridal Planner Group's Right to Contact User

Bridal Planner Group reserves the right to contact site visitors regarding account status and changes to the subscriber agreement, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to site visitors.

9\. Bridal Planner Group's Right to Change Privacy Policy

The foregoing policy is effective as of April 1, 2005. Bridal Planner Group reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy. By entering the Bridal Planner Group website you are accepting all terms and conditions outlined in the above New York City Weddings, Inc Internet Privacy Policy.
